Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Now we have to defeat their leader? What's with the sword?
Lict had awakened from his centuries-long slumber, overwhelming Asa and Yuno with his devastating strength and magic power.
You're not killing Yuno!
For us to either!
He's my rival!
Even their perfectly coordinated simultaneous attack had no effect on their foe.
Well, about that time. Let's go pay the rest of our friends a visit, and then we'll wipe out all humankind.
After escaping from the hideout by the skin of their teeth, Asa and Yuno joined forces with their friends and hurried toward the capital, determined to save the Clover Kingdom and return the Possessed Magic Knights to Normum. However...
Poison plant magic, now Zoffnir's Garden of Lingering Birds!
But that's... the village!
The pair soon realized that their hometown was under attack by elven forces.
Stop!
Oh no! Stay back!
Master!
You know!
You're really brave, Nash. Good job!
Stay back! It's our turn now!
Turn now!
欲しくなりそうな方へ 一緒に走っていこうね
いつの間にか 君の背中へ 遠く感じてる
青い空にシャツが揺れる
未来向かい and blue 痛むきに cry and fight
だから待って待って待って待って 置いてかないでてよ
今すぐfly away 戦む try again
だから待って待って待って 同じ場所にいたいよ
風もに抱いたい胸の痛みが 君に話したい僕の気持ちが
本当のことね baby firelight
次回予告
So you blocked my attack nicely done
You must be magic knight just like the previous owner of this body was
Let's see what will you do next?
Poison plant magic Zofnir's breath and Zofnir's fingers for good measure
I wonder will you succumb to poison the way they did or will you be impaled?
Your choice
Not happening
Look at them now! They're strong!
It's a miracle!
Those two were left at the church on the same day
They grew up in this village
And then the two of them set off courageously into the world with their aspirations to become the wizard king
They've grown into such capable young men and now they're here to save Haj village
Asta told me once
If you don't give up you can achieve your dreams
You can make everybody happy
Yes
They may have been gone for a while
But we've still kept them in our hearts
And we know they've been working hard toward their goal of becoming wizard king
Thank you
I knew we were right about you, Yuno!
The pride and joy of Haj
Making it into the magic knights
Not that I'm surprised
Yuno can do anything!
Yeah, anything!
Everyone in the village will be so excited when they hear
And what does Asta's letter say?
Can you even make out that terrible chicken scratch of his?
Yeah, he writes like a five-year-old
So does he say when he's coming home?
When he does get here, we'll have to cheer him up
Even Asta will have a hard time bouncing back from this
Maybe a paw potato party will lift his spirits
Actually, he says that he got in
They both passed
What?
Seriously?
Mm-hmm
Oh wow
You're not kidding, are you?
Really?
He did it!
So, um...
I guess that...
Asta won't be coming home
Will he?
Right!
We'll go let everyone know about our magic knights!
This will be the best news Haj Village has ever gotten!
Amazing!
He's gonna be a magic knight just like he said!
He did it!
As time went on, the occasional letters from Asta and Yuno became a special treat that we all looked forward to
How's it going, Sister Lily?
Is there anything new going on with Nash and the rest of the gang lately?
My first assignment as a member of the Black Bulls was to go boar hunting!
But we ended up running into this mysterious bad guy who was super tough!
You stand no chance of prevailing against me
Why not accept that and give up?
If I gave up now, then who would protect them?
I realized something...
Hmm?
Sooner or later, I'm going to be the Wizard King!
But it's not just about keeping a promise
It's about keeping people safe!
You ready, Asta?
Here we go!
All the magic power I've got left!
Now, my soul ball!
Go ball!
Huh?
Flame magic!
Prison death!
Scatter shots!
This is the final spell of your pathetic life?
What a complete waste
Your time is up
You quit!
That wasn't the real attack
He's reflecting the spells!
Not done yet!
As long as I can still move, I'm not done!
No! You can't!
Like hell!
We managed to win the battle somehow
But we couldn't prevent him from destroying himself in the end
And we weren't able to keep all the villagers safe either
I can tell it's going to be a long road to becoming the Wizard King
But no matter how hard things may get, I'll never give up!
Never giving up is the one thing he's better at than anybody else
Go get him, Asta!
Yeah, go!
No!
And one more thing
Please, Sister Lily, can we get married someday?
Asta!
He hasn't changed a bit, has he?
I do know she'd give up on that, though
Sister Lily, can you read Yuno's letter now?
Read it! Read it!
Yuno!
I can read that one myself, if you don't mind
Let's see here
Greetings, everyone
I visited Magic Knight's headquarters the other day
Where I got to meet the Wizard King
Sincerely, Yuno
So cool!
What's the letter say after that?
Uh, it looks like that's all of it
Yuno's letters are always so short and to the point
I've noticed that
There's a lot more detail in Asta's writing
He says,
Me and Yuno went to headquarters to give a report about our mission
No!
Is that really?
I never dreamed you'd greet us personally, sir
Huh?
He's flashy
Who do you think this guy is?
YOU IDIOT!
This is none other than the current Wizard King
Sir Julius Novacrono
It's actually him
The Wizard King!
Anyway, well done
You did a marvelous job out there
Much appreciated
Uh, uh, just
Can I...
Can I maybe ask you something, sir?
Sure, what is it?
I was just wondering
How can I become the Wizard King?
I see, so the two of you are looking to become the Wizard King, are you?
Not surprising given that you are a Magic Knight
You two must realize how rude it is to ask a question like that so directly
Now listen
The Wizard King must be of noble heart and have the implicit trust of all of his people
No, Klaus
It's about results
A noble heart alone cannot protect anyone
And the trust of the people is earned, not granted
You want to know what you need to do to gain the title of Wizard King?
Get results
Prove that you're the strongest
Do what it takes
Devote yourself to getting results
That's all there is
Anyone who's not capable of that cannot hope to stand at the summit
Exactly what I wanted to hear
Devote yourself to getting results
The way he said it was simple
But his words really stuck with me
I'm gonna get results on top of results
As much as I can
Those two are working hard in a completely different world
A place those of us in the Forsaken Realm can't even imagine
Hearing about their accomplishments always filled us with so much courage and hope
But then
Dear Hajj Village
I'm about to go explore the underwater temple at the bottom of the sea
We didn't know why
But that was the last bit of correspondence we received from Asta for quite some time
We told ourselves no news is good news
Since that's what the old adage says
But after Asta's letter stopped coming in
We found ourselves worrying about his safety more and more
When a message did eventually arrive
We were shocked at what we saw
It was pages and pages long
Almost like he'd written down everything that had ever happened in his life
To everyone in the village
I'm sorry I haven't written to you in a long time
Don't get me wrong
I really wanted to
I just couldn't
Asta told us the story of a fierce battle against the Eye of the Midnight Sun in the underwater temple
And explained that both of his arms had been rendered useless by curse magic
When he received an examination, the doctor said he would never write a letter again, much less hold a sword
His fellow black bulls learned about his predicament and set off on a relentless search for a cure
Then, he wrote that he had gone to the forest of witches where the queen cast a spell that rid him of his curse
My magic is never giving up!
So, do you have this big dramatic transformation?
Did you expect me to be impressed by that or something?
That hurt something!
You're mine!
Ah
what are you how the hell is this happening i want you out of my side
it's not fair i stepped on so many people to go where i am now i can't lose to you
you always kicked your friends down but my friends helped me be better stronger
not long after that both asta and yuno wrote to us about their excellent showing at the star
festival and how they'd won the approval of those in the royal capital hearing of their success made
our hearts glow with pride my that certainly was an exciting entrance wasn't it let's all applaud
for the rookie who's done the most for the black bulls this year oh shucks thank you guys
yuno and asta are the top earners among all of the novice knights which means they are two new stars
to watch they've produced outstanding results considering the fact they've only been knights
for half a year interestingly these 16 year olds are childhood friends from the same hometown for
being so young those two are doing marvelous things yeah they're probably nobility actually they're not
but commoners huh it's true haha the scrawny guy from the black bulls doesn't even have any magic isn't
that so sad commoners really he can't use magic makes you wonder if they really earned those stars
that's so rude what is the matter with these people bell what is it you know let's show them
it'd be my pleasure
what are you about to do asta remember how we used to train back when we were little kids
yeah but
why do you always have to pull crazy stuff like this on me out of nowhere
you're stronger now what are you trying to kill me during my 15 seconds of fame you big jerk
if that had killed you we'd know what your limit was good thing you survived
why you little oh that magic power was devastating he blocked it
they're shockingly strong i invite anyone who still doubts their worthiness to please step forward
now that you've witnessed their abilities yes it's true these two are commoners
but they've worked harder than any of their peers to make it where they are today
proud citizens of the clover kingdom let us commend these brave knights
regardless of rank or status our nation's path to victory is to join together as one
wizard king
commoners aren't so bad
hear hear
this is no time to dwell on our differences
we can all fight together
you know
yeah
look at us
we've really come this far
it's me again guys
someday
i'll become the wizard king
every time i cut it down it grows back
if we keep going like this we'll never get anywhere
father
hang in there
please don't die okay
poison
the demon slayer sword can fix that
just like it did before right
hey yuno
can i leave it to you for now
yeah i'm fine
i can win this with my eyes closed
he's all yours then i gotta do something real quick
hold on
afta please help
he protected us and he ended up getting hurt
here goes
why didn't it work
he's not under any spell
this is bad news
the magics run its course and the poison spread through his body
i'm so scared
i think this is the end
you can't give up so soon just stay with me
it's all right
in the end
i got to see you and yuno again
all grown up and strong
that's enough for me
i'll think of it as
god's reward for the deeds i've done
don't talk like that
our little asta
i'm so proud
take care of them
for me
father
no
not yet
you're not done yet you hear me
don't die
you can't die
you were supposed to stick around for a while to watch over us
to see me through
to see all of us through
that sword
it's his
i saw it back at the midnight sun's hideout
it must have slipped into my grimoire somehow
maybe if i use it
i can
how do you think about it
to be tried it
Sometimes, excuse me,
I was up for a second.
I can't talk more about it.
letzten words,
like it,
Unused bad feelings.
Thank you very much for having me.
I don't need no money
I don't need no魔力は要らない
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い
魅力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ
切り込んでく世界を巻き込んでく
My disability is my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って
嫌いになって
負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく
Our treasure
裏切らないのは
最後にThere is love
かざした近い光が
生きるTREASURE
ご視聴ありがとうございました